[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Різноманітний' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "色んな"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Подорож' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "旅"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Листочок' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "葉っぱ"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ікебана (мистецтво квітів)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "生け花"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Смажений батат' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "焼き芋"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Справи' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "用事"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Д,З' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "宿題"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Жахіття' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "大変"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Автобусна зупинка' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "バス停"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Охоронець, вахта' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "門番"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Стояти у ряд' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "並びます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Національний' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "国立"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the word 'Наприклад' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "例えば"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the word 'Урок' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "授業"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the word 'Простий' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "簡単(な）"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the word 'Солодощі' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "お菓子"
    }
]